# **Brandon**Ayers

- brandonayers@gmail.com
- **3** 850.530.2999
- Austin, TX
- brandonayers.com

### **OVERVIEW**

A lifelong hobby of exploring / exploiting systems and technology, turned into a decades long career at the intersection of mobile tech and advertising.

An experienced executive with an undying passion for mobile, solutioning interesting problems, fostering products and growing relationships.

## **FOCUS**

Mobile Product Strategy

Relationship Management

Product/Feature Expansion

Permission Exploitation

Hacking and Experimentation Android, iOS, Connected TV, Tizen, SIM Applet, Linux, WebOS, etc.

## **EDUCATION**

Digital Enterprise

#### **University of West Florida**

- E September 2000
- Pensacola, FL

# **Experience**

VP, Strategy / R&D

#### **Digital Turbine**

Feb 2020 - Present | Austin, TX

- Principal advisor to the CEO on strategic direction and initiatives for a
  growing suite of intersecting mobile products and services, including:
  integrated on-device products, mobile advertising, mobile gaming,
  alternative billing, etc.
- Head of DT Labs group, focused on the exploration and development of novel products, features and services for partners and consumers
- Close collaborator with product owners to maximize engagement and performance across the portfolio
- Owner and manager of strategic relationships for key accounts and partnerships; directly impacting account growth, product expansion, etc.
- Critical contributor to due diligence processes, identifying acquisition targets, and providing analysis, guiding strategic investment decisions
- Directly responsible for the majority of the company's issued and pending intellectual property

## Director, Strategy & Partnerships

#### **Digital Turbine**

Oct 2014 - Feb 2020 | Austin, TX

- Identification of opportunities to grow and expand product and feature suite for new and existing telco partners
- Exploration of technical feasibility / product-market fit, requiring collaboration with technical and business development leadership
- Primary strategic and technical interface between internal stakeholders and telco partners
- Continuity oversight and management for partner onboarding and product launches

## Manager, Mobile Ad Product

#### Gannett / USA Today

Nov 2005 - April 2014 | Washington, DC

- Oversaw global roadmap(s) for advertising products across portfolio of news and content applications (75+)
- Produced and managed performance analysis and projections for pre and post launch products
- Managed partnerships for strategic and revenue generating integrations eg. SDK etc.